{
  "shortDescription": "Test your knowledge of Curb Your Enthusiasm.",
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "Who is Larry?",
      "answers": ["Creator", "Actor", "Writer"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is Jeff?",
      "answers": ["Agent", "Friend", "Neighbor"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Latte Larry's?",
      "answers": ["Cafe", "Bar", "Store"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is Cheryl?",
      "answers": ["Wife", "Sister", "Cousin"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is Susie?",
      "answers": ["Jeff's", "Larry's", "Cheryl's"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is Leon?",
      "answers": ["Roomie", "Agent", "Friend"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is HBO?",
      "answers": ["Network", "Channel", "Show"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is spite store?",
      "answers": ["Rival", "Cafe", "Bar"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is Richard?",
      "answers": ["Friend", "Agent", "Cousin"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is Marty?",
      "answers": ["Friend", "Brother", "Neighbor"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Seinfeld?",
      "answers": ["Show", "Actor", "Writer"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is Ted?",
      "answers": ["Friend", "Agent", "Neighbor"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is Funkhouser?",
      "answers": ["Friend", "Agent", "Writer"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is Vince?",
      "answers": ["Neighbor", "Agent", "Friend"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is big penis sketch?",
      "answers": ["Scene", "Show", "Joke"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Larry's sandwich?",
      "answers": ["Order", "Menu", "Dish"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is Jerry?",
      "answers": ["Friend", "Actor", "Writer"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is fake heart attack?",
      "answers": ["Prank", "Act", "Scene"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is Loretta?",
      "answers": ["Ex-girl", "Neighbor", "Agent"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Larry's bald cap?",
      "answers": ["Prop", "Hat", "Wig"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    }
  ]
}
